http://www.designcouncil.org.uk/privacy-policy

Sign in
Forgotten your password?
Privacy & cookie policy
Design Council respects and protects the privacy of people who use Design Council's website (the “Website”). Individually available information about you is not disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this Privacy Policy.
What information do we collect and how do we use it?
Design Council does not collect any unique information about you (such as your name, e-mail address etc), except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.
Design Council collects data when you register to receive our email newsletter or via the completion of other sign up forms. We collect this data, via the email address provided, to share with you relevant Design Council/industry related content, namely:
Blogs and website articles produced by Design Council on programme and industry related topics
Newsletters – a periodically produced Design Council news bulletin
Trade Articles – news/articles featuring Design Council programme, product, policy or procedure
Event information – news of upcoming events that we feel would be of interest to you.
Industry and partnership offers, events and discounts that we feel would be of interest to you.
Your details are securely stored on our CRM System and email database. By providing personal details during registration you are consenting to the use of those details for the purposes of identifying you as a unique user.
The information you provide when registering will not be shared with any other entity or organisation, without your explicit consent, aside from our service providers who operate elements of our service and process data on our behalf, and apart from your username, which will appear on blog entries, submissions to forums and other submissions you make for inclusion on the website.
We will not use the information submitted through the registration process on the Website for any other purpose if you indicate that you do not want us to, and we will not pass your contact details to any third party for the purpose of making any marketing communication to you without having first received your explicit consent.
All data collected will be held within the European Union and the European Economic Area or other territory complying with the legal and technical guidelines laid down for handling data by the European Union and will only be used for the specific purpose for which it was sought and to which you consented. It will not be used for any other purpose whatsoever. Any personal data we hold on you will be deleted or updated upon request and any inaccurate or misleading data held will be changed or deleted upon your request.
Details of the data we hold on you will be provided on request. Any request of this nature should be directed to the e-mail address shown at the bottom of this notice.
As required by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) the Design Council follows strict security procedures in relation to the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us, to prevent unauthorised access or use of such data. In the event, however, that the Design Council or its officers or employees are required to undertake any act under the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act or similar legislation the Design Council or such person shall be entitled and occasionally obliged to do so without informing you. We would also ask that in such circumstances you co-operate with the Design Council.
You have the right to access any of the information held about you by emailing: info@designcouncil.org.uk
You have the right to unsubscribe from our database by selecting unsubscribe option at the bottom of any of our communications or by contacting info@designcouncil.org.uk
Cookies
The Design Council does note and save information such as time of day, browser type and content requested when you visit our website. This information is used to provide more relevant services to users. We do this by placing a piece of code on each web page. This provides statistical site usage information relating solely to Internet usage behaviour.
We may also use 'Cookies' to collect other information that is not personal information (i.e. it will not identify you). Cookies are a means by which information relating to your internet activity (such as whether you have visited the Website before) is recorded on your hard drive and used by us to improve the Website. For example, Cookies may be used to gather statistical information that will assist in understanding what users find interesting and useful on the Website.
These Cookies are known as your 'Unique Visitor Cookie', which is a small piece of data or a number that identifies your computer. This information cannot be used to identify you. This data is sent to your browser from a Web server and then stored onto your computer's hard drive. Through modification of browser preferences, a user can elect to accept all Cookie, receive notification when a cookie is set or decline all Cookies.
For further assistance in disabling Cookies, please consult your web browser’s “Help” file or visit the website at www.allaboutcookies.org.
Links to other sites
The websites linked to the Design Council's are developed by people over whom Design Council exercises no control. These sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. We give no warranty or indemnity in relation to the content appearing on those websites or in relation to the administration of these websites.
With whom does Design Council share information?
Design Council will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent.
Who can I ask if I have additional questions?
Design Council will answer any additional questions you may have. Contact our Data Protection Lead, John Middleton, at the following email address: info@designcouncil.org.uk
Home
Who we areOur mission
Our impact
Our history
Our people
Our governance
Diversity and Inclusion
What we doStrategic Advice
